Guide to the John G. Franclemont papers,1939-1994.
Francelmont, John G. Papers, 1939-1994
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
John G. Franclemont papers, 1939-1994.
21-01-3556
John G. Franclemont
2 cubic ft.
Correspondence.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
The collection consists of correspondence name files and correspondence filed alphabetically.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Professor John G. Franclemont taught in the Department of Entomology; he focused his research on the moths of North America, with particular interest in cutworms. His personal collection of insects contained more than 350,000 specimens, which he donated to the Cornell University Insect Collection. He received his bachelors degree (1935) and doctorate (1953) both from Cornell. He served as entomologist in the Bureau of Entomology and Plant Quarantine, U. S. Department of Agriculture in Washington, D. C. from 1947-1952. He joined the Cornell faculty as assistant professor on February 1, 1953. Three months later he was promoted to associate professor. He became full professor in 1959 and professor emeritus in 1977.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The collection consists of correspondence name files and correspondence filed alphabetically.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Franclemont, John G.; Cornell University--Faculty.; New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences.Dept. of Entomology.
Subjects:
Entomologists.; Entomology--Study and teaching.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Series: Correspondence Files
  - Adams, M.S., 1984-1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ahmadi, Ali Asghar, 1975-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Arnett, Ross H., Jr., 1981-1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ball, George E., 1991 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Big Bend National Park, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Brou, Vernon A., 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Brown, Richard L., 1974-1991 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Buckett, J.S., 1966-1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Clarke, J.F. Gates, 1960-1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Classey, Eric W., 1971-1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Classey, Eric W., 1968-1986 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Covelli, C.V., Jr., 1975-1986 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Dalgleish, Robert C., 1966-1984 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Davis, Donald R., 1966-1992 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Dickel, Terhume S., 1984-1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Donahue, Julian P., 1972-1982 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Eberhard, William G., 1982 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Entomography, 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Ferguson, Douglas C., 1949-1962 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Ferguson, Douglas C., 1962-1972 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Ferguson, Douglas C., 1972-1994 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Field, William D., 1968 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Fletcher, D.S., 1974-1980 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Forestry Service Southwest, 1964-1967 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Frechin, Don, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Furth, David G., 1979-1983 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Gall, L.F. and Hawks, D.C., 1988-1990 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Ginsberg, Howard, 1981-1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Godfrey, George L., 1970-1992 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Hardwick, David F., 1961-1990 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Hayes, Alan H., 1974-1985 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Heitzman, Richard, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Heitzman, Roger L., 1980 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Heppner, John-Neotropiccal, 1970-1980 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Heppner, John B., 1979-1982 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Hodges, Elaine-Moth Book Drawings, 1958-1973 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Hodges, Elaine-Moth Book Drawings, 1973-1993 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Hodges, Ronald W., 1959-1964 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Hoebeke, E.R., 1974-1991 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Honey, Martin R. (British Museum-Natural History), 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Jacobson, Nancy, 1988-1989 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Kendall, Roy D., 1969-1971 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Knowlton, G.F. (Utah Insects), 1939-1940 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Krasnoff, Stuart B., 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Leuschner, Ron, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Martin, Lloyd M., 1956-1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Matthews, Marcus J., 1983-1986 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - McCabe, Tim L., 1974-1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - McCabe, Tim L., 1990-1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - McFarland, Noel, 1979-1985 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Metzler, Eric H., 1984-1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Meyer, Wendy, 1982-1984 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Miller, James S., 1980-1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Munroe, E.G., 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Nabokov, Vladimir, 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Nielsen, M.C., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Nye, I.W.B.-Noctuidae Names, 1972-1983 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Nye, I.W.B., 1968-1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Poole, Robert W., 1966-1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Powell, Jerry A., 1967-1968 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Quinter, Eric L., 1972-1991 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Ramberg, Frank B., 1974-1983 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Rawlins, John E., 1973-1993 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Rindge, Frederick H., 1949-1987 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Robertson, Ron, 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Rupert, Laurence R., 1973 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Sabrosky, Curtis W., 1967 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Schweitzer, Dale F., 1986 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Smedley, Scott, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Solis, Maria Alma, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Sugi, Shigero, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Todd, Edward L.-U.S. National Museum, 1951-1962 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Todd, Edward L.-U.S. National Museum, 1962-1976 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Todd, Edward L.-Misc. Correspondence, 1970-1980 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Warren, Andrew, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Watson, Allan (British Museum/Natural Museum), 1969-1987 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Weintraub, Jason D., 1984-1988 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Various Correspondence, 1981-1990 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Various Correspondence, 1990-1993 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Ab-Al, 1946-1980 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Adams, Sam and Delia, 1973-1994 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - American Camera Exchange, 1956-1960 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Am, 1940-1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - American Entomological Society, 1943-1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - American Philosophical Society, 1955-1963 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - An, 1948-1975 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Anderson, Don M., 1961-1970 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Anderson, Lauren D., 1966-1969 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Anderson, William H., 1952-1969 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Antiquariaat Junk, 1939-1982 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Ap-Az, 1946-2000 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Appleton-Century-Crofts, 1968-1972 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Archbold, Richard, 1954-1962 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Arnett, Ross H., Jr., 1942-1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Arnold, Richard A., 1972-1978 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Arntz, Arnold, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - A, Asher and Co., 1948-1961 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Ayers, George S., 1962 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Ba, 1941-1994 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Ball, George E., 1947-1994 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Bauer, William, 1941-1960 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Be, 1946-1988 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Beard, Robert, 1965-1969 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Becker, E. C., 1962-1974 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Belkin, John, 1942-1963 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Bell, Ernest L., 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Belmont, Robert A., 1975 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Berg, Clifford O., 1969-1973 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Berio, Emilio, 1952-1986 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Berry, Dean F., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Bi-Bl, 1936-1984 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Bio Metal Associates, 1948-1993 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Blanchard, A., 1962-1984 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Bo, 1946-1986 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Boone, Peter, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Bourgogne, J., 1948-49 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Boursin, Charles, 1952-1957 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Bowers, Deane, 1972-1982 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Bowman, Kenneth, 1942-1949 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Boynton, Damon, 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Br-Bri, 1941-1980 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Bradley, J. Chester, 1950-1975 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Bridwell, Louis H., 1940-1951 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - British Museum Of Natural History, 1946-1980 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Bro, 1951-1996 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Brooklyn Entomological Society, 1944-1964 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Brower, A. E., 1934-1967 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Brower, L. P., 1972 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Brown, Keith, Jr., 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Brown, Richard L., 1967-1994 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Brown, W. J., 1940-1947 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Brown, William L., 1957-1969 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Bru-By, 1940-1981 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Bruggemann, Paul F., 1942-1955 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - Bruner, S. C., 1947-1948 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Buchholz, Otto, 1939-1949 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Buckett, Steve, 1962-1965 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - Burch, John Q., 1947-1958 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Byers, George W., 1957-1981 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Ca, 1941-1992 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Cadbury, John W., 1936-1955 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Calora, F. B., 1958-1971 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Calvert, Philip P., 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Carlson, Donald, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Capps, Hahn W., 1946-1963 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Carnegie Museum Pittsburgh, Pa., 1947-1982 (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Carolina Biological Supply, 1955-1975 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Carpenter, F. M., 1947-1960 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Carruth, L. A., 1959-1963 (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Cartwright, O. L., 1957-1969 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Cazier, Mont A., 1953-1955 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Ce-Ch, 1940-1991 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Cekalovic K., Tomas, 1952-1961 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Chamberlain, K. F., 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Chapin, Edward A., 1942-1960 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Chapman, P. J., 1958-1960 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - China, W. E., 1963-1966 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Chu, Linda Yu-ling, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Cl, 1948-1974 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Clarke, J. F. Gates, 1936-1974 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Clarke-Macintyre, William, 1939-1949 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Classey, Eric W., 1950-1992 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Clausen, Robert T., 1961-1963 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Clench, Harry K., 1953-1958 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Coc-Com, 1941-1981 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Coleopterists' Society, 1964-2001 (Box 3, Folder 87)
  - Commonwealth Institute of Entomology, 1949-1961 (Box 3, Folder 88)
  - Compagnie Orientale Francaise, Ltd., 1939 (Box 3, Folder 89)
  - Comstock, John A., 1939-1967 (Box 3, Folder 90)
  - Comstock, William P., 1940-1949 (Box 3, Folder 91)
  - Con-Coy, 1941-1987 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Cooke, W. Donald, 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Cook, William C., 1945-1955 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Cooper, K. W., 1954-1956 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Covell, Charles V., Jr., 1960-1985 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Cr-Cz, 1944-1999 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Crabill, Ralph E., Jr., 1954-1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Creighton, William S., 1960 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Cresson, Ezra T., 1939-1942 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Crumb, S. E., 1941-1958 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Crummy, Pressley L., 1947 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Czech, Jerry H., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Da, 1966-1988 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Dahlem, Gregory A., 1988 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Dalgleish, Robert C., 1966-1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Dampf, Alfons, 1939-1942 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Darlington, P. J., 1952-1960 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Davis, Don, 1955-1983 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - De, 1953-1992 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Walter De Gruyter, Inc., 1946-2000 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - De la Torre, Salvador L., 1963 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - De Lajonquière, Yves, 1970-1976 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - De Worms, Charles, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - De Zayas, Ing. F., 1952-1956 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Denning, D. G., 1950 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Di, 1959-1994 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Diakonoff, Alex A, 1948-1962 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Dickel, Terry, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Dietrich, Henry, 1942-1962 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Dietz, Robert, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Dirig, Robert E., 1963-1996 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Do-Dy, 1940-1990 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Doll, Marie, 1958-1970 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Donahue, Julian P., 1964-1998 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Dos Passos, Cyril F., 1940-1961 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Dow, Richard, 1937-1941 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Downey, John C., 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Duckworth, W. D., 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Dybas, Henry S., 1972-1977 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Ea-Em, 1948-1983 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - The Ealing Corporation, 1960-1962 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Eastern Model Aircraft Co., 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Eastman Kodak Company, 1938-1968 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Eberhard, William G., 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Edmund Scientific Corporation, 1953-1969 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Ehrlich, Paul R., 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Eichlin, Thomas D., 1967-1973 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Eickwort, George C., 1967-1980 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Eisner, Thomas, 1960-1977 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - Ekis, Ginter, 1980-1982 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - George D. Ellis and Sons, Inc., 1950-1960 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - Emsley, M. G., 1963-1969 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - En-Ey, 1941-1995 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - Engel, Henry, 1937-1942 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - Entomological Society of America, 1952-1985 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - Entomological Society of Canada, 1957-1983 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - Entomological Society of Ontario, 1943-1983 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - Entomological Society of Southern Africa, 1946-1975 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Entomological Society of Washington, 1947-1982 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - The Entomologist's Monthly Magazine, 1954-1955 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - The Entomologist's Record, 1948-1954 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - Erskine, Katherine F., 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Escalante, Tarsicio, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Escher, Susan, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Etcheverry, Maria, 1951-1965 (Box 4, Folder 65)
  - Evans, Howard E., 1952-1990 (Box 4, Folder 66)
  - Evans, Mark H., 1985 (Box 4, Folder 67)
  - Evans, William H., 1950-1951 (Box 4, Folder 68)
  - The Exakta Company, Inc., 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 69)
  - Eyer, John R., 1962-1975 (Box 4, Folder 70)
  - Fa-Fi, 1939-1980 (Box 4, Folder 71)
  - Ferguson, Douglass, 1952-1994 (Box 4, Folder 72)
  - Ferguson, E. A., 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 73)
  - Ferreira d'Almeida, R., 1946-1955 (Box 4, Folder 74)
  - Fiedler, Henry George, 1940-1957 (Box 4, Folder 75)
  - Field, William D., 1941-1971 (Box 4, Folder 76)
  - Field Museum of Natural History, Chicago, 1942-1969 (Box 4, Folder 77)
  - Fischer, Richard B., 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 78)
  - Fischer, Roland L., 1955-1972 (Box 4, Folder 79)
  - Fitch, Richard J., 1941-1958 (Box 4, Folder 80)
  - Fl-Fo, 1951-1986 (Box 4, Folder 81)
  - Fletcher, D. S., 1950-1962 (Box 4, Folder 82)
  - Flint, Oliver S., Jr., 1959-1981 (Box 4, Folder 83)
  - Flynn, Kenneth F., 1948-1964 (Box 4, Folder 84)
  - Foote, Richard, 1964-1973 (Box 4, Folder 85)
  - Forbes, WMT, 1942-1947 (Box 4, Folder 86)
  - Forbes, WMT, 1948-1966 (Box 4, Folder 87)
  - Ford, A., 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 88)
  - Ford, Robert, 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 89)
  - Forster, Walter, 1955-1959 (Box 4, Folder 90)
  - Forsythe, Margnerite S., 1946 (Box 4, Folder 91)
  - Fox, Richard M., 1964-1966 (Box 4, Folder 92)
  - Fr-Fur, 1949-1982 (Box 4, Folder 93)
  - Freeman, T. N., 1947-1971 (Box 4, Folder 94)
  - R. Friedlander and Sohn, 1960-1972 (Box 4, Folder 95)
  - Frost, S. W., 1958-1979 (Box 4, Folder 96)
  - Furth, David, 1951-1981 (Box 4, Folder 97)
  - Ga-Gi, 1940-1991 (Box 4, Folder 98)
  - Gardner, J. C. M., 1946-1947 (Box 4, Folder 99)
  - William J. Gerhard, 1939-1941 (Box 4, Folder 100)
  - Gibbon, Hugh A., 1941 (Box 4, Folder 101)
  - Gl-Gra, 1949-1986 (Box 4, Folder 102)
  - Glanz, A./Butterfly World Supply House, 1932-1946 (Box 4, Folder 103)
  - Glenn, Murray O., 1953-1966 (Box 4, Folder 104)
  - Godfrey, George, 1970-1976 (Box 4, Folder 105)
  - Goldsmith Brothers, 1961-1964 (Box 4, Folder 106)
  - Gotwald, Bill, 1966-1968 (Box 4, Folder 107)
  - Graf, J. E., 1942-1946 (Box 4, Folder 108)
  - Grant, Harold J., Jr., 1960-1966 (Box 4, Folder 109)
  - Grant, J. A., 1965 (Box 4, Folder 110)
  - Gravelle, Paul, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 111)
  - Grayson, James McD., 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 112)
  - Gre-Gu, 1941-1980 (Box 4, Folder 113)
  - Green, Ray, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 114)
  - Gressitt, J. Linsley, 1941-1970 (Box 4, Folder 115)
  - Grey, L. P., 1953-1982 (Box 4, Folder 116)
  - Guedet, E., 1935-1940 (Box 4, Folder 117)
  - Gyrisco, George G., 1962-1981 (Box 4, Folder 118)
  - Ha-Hay, 1941-1996 (Box 4, Folder 119)
  - Handfield, Louis, 1983-1988 (Box 4, Folder 120)
  - Hanneman, H. J., 1972 (Box 4, Folder 121)
  - Hansen, Jean R., 1970 (Box 4, Folder 122)
  - Hanson, Bror, 1964-1966 (Box 4, Folder 123)
  - Hanson, W. J., 1963-1964 (Box 4, Folder 124)
  - Hardwick, D. F., 1950-1986 (Box 4, Folder 125)
  - Harvard, 1946-1982 (Box 4, Folder 126)
  - Hawkins, John, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 127)
  - Hayes, Alan H., 1963-1971 (Box 4, Folder 128)
  - He, 1941-1984 (Box 4, Folder 129)
  - Heinrich, Bernd, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 130)
  - Heinrich, Carl, 1941-1947 (Box 4, Folder 131)
  - Hemming, Francis, 1955-1957 (Box 4, Folder 132)
  - Henne, Christopher, 1968-1972 (Box 4, Folder 133)
  - Heppner, John B., 1970-1999 (Box 4, Folder 134)
  - Herman, Lee H., 1968-1974 (Box 4, Folder 135)
  - Herrera-Gonzalez, José, 1950-1961 (Box 4, Folder 136)
  - Herring, Jon L., 1966-1967 (Box 4, Folder 137)
  - Hessel, Sidney, 1950-1957 (Box 4, Folder 138)
  - Heydemann, F., 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 139)
  - Hi-Ho, 1941-1983 (Box 4, Folder 140)
  - Hill, Charles, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 141)
  - Himalayan Butterfly Company, 1938-1948 (Box 4, Folder 142)
  - Hirashima, Yoshihiro, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 143)
  - Hodges, Ron and Elaine, 1961-2004 (Box 4, Folder 144)
  - Hoebeke, E. Richard, 1973-1984 (Box 4, Folder 145)
  - Hogue, Charles L., 1959-1970 (Box 4, Folder 146)
  - Hone, H., 1951 (Box 4, Folder 147)
  - Howell, Thelma, 1957-1997 (Box 4, Folder 148)
  - Hr-Hu, 1948-1994 (Box 4, Folder 149)
  - Hudson, George V., 1941-1946 (Box 4, Folder 150)
  - Hurd, Paul D., Jr., 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 151)
  - Hutton, James K., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 152)
  - Huxley, John, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 153)
  - Correspondence I, 1974-1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Imperial Institute of Entomology, 1946-1948 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Inove, H., 1949-1956 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Insect Museum Supply, 1965-1976 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Insects of Micronesia, 1952-1954 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - International Commission on Zoological Nomenclature, 1946-1960 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Ja-Je, 1953-1982 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Jacot-Guillarmod, Francois, 1961-1969 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - James, Maurice T., 1941-1955 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Janzen, Daniel H., 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - JB Indexes, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Jennejohn, Edward, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Jo-Ju, 1940-1998 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Johnson, John, 1960-1978 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Johnson, Kurt, 1994-1998 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Johnston, Edward C., 1941-1948 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Jones, Frank M., 1938-1950 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Jordan, Karl, 1948-1950 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Joseph, G.H., 1965 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Jugatae, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Junk, W., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Ka-Ki, 1946-1999 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Keene, Cecil E., 1941 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Kelsheimer, E.G., 1954-1956 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Kennedy, W. Keith, 1972-1992 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Verlag, Alfred Kernen, 1950-1976 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Kian, Liem Ping, 1946-1962 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Kimball, Charles P., 1939-1963 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Kimball, Charles P., 1964-1981 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Kimmins, D.E., 1970 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - King, James C., 1946-1974 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Kiriakoff, Sergius G., 1951-1970 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Kirk, John G., 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Kl-Kw, 1948-1976 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Kloet, G.S., 1947 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Klots, Alexander B., 1941-1972 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Knight, Ken L., 1947-1958 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Knowles, H.E., 1954-1960 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - Knowlton, C.B., 1959-1970 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Knudson, Edward C., 1981-1986 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Knutson, Lloyd, 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Koeltz, Otto, Antiquariatsbuchhandlung, 1951-1961 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Kohler, Pablo, 1946-1980 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Kosztarab, Michael, 1962-1965 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Kraus Periodicals, Inc., 1968-1970 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Krivda, Walter, 1960-1985 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Krombein, Karl, 1936-1942 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Krombein, Karl, 1943-1952 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Krombein, Karl, 1953-1980 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Kuitert, Louis, 1942-1957 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - La, 1940-1995 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - Labrador, S., Jose Ramon, 1953 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  - Laffoon, Jean L., 1958-1970 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - Lamas, Gerardo, 1973-1981 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - Lane Science Equipment Corp., 1968-1984 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - Lange, W. Harry, 1950-1963 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - Latham, Roy, 1953-1965 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Laubengayer, Dorothy, 1963-1965 (Box 5, Folder 58)
  - Le-Lu, 1955-1995 (Box 5, Folder 59)
  - Leech, Hugh B., 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 60)
  - Lemmer, Frederick, 1934-1941 (Box 5, Folder 61)
  - Lempke, B.J., 1948-1952 (Box 5, Folder 62)
  - Lennox, Donald J., 1941-1948 (Box 5, Folder 63)
  - Leonard, M.D., 1945-1970 (Box 5, Folder 64)
  - Lepidopterists' Society, 1955-1993 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Leuschner, Ron, 1952-1993 (Box 5, Folder 66)
  - Levatich, Julius, 1965-1976 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - Lichy, Rene, 1939-1951 (Box 5, Folder 68)
  - Liebherr, Jim, 1974-1995 (Box 5, Folder 69)
  - Lienk, S.E., 1955-1959 (Box 5, Folder 70)
  - Linsley, E.G., 1949-1962 (Box 5, Folder 71)
  - Lundberg, Eric, 1951-1966 (Box 5, Folder 72)
  - M-Ma, 1940-1982 (Box 5, Folder 73)
  - Macalaster-Bicknell, 1956-1968 (Box 5, Folder 74)
  - Marshall, James D., 1961-1967 (Box 5, Folder 75)
  - Marshall, John, 1954-1955 (Box 5, Folder 76)
  - Martin, J.E.H., 1977 (Box 5, Folder 77)
  - Martin, Lloyd, 1957-1982 (Box 5, Folder 78)
  - Mason, W.R.M., 1948-1961 (Box 5, Folder 79)
  - Mather, Bryant, 1960-1961 (Box 5, Folder 80)
  - Matheson, Robert, 1942-1949 (Box 5, Folder 81)
  - Matthews, Eric G., 1961-1963 (Box 5, Folder 82)
  - Matthyse, J.G., 1955-1973 (Box 5, Folder 83)
  - Mattoni, Rudolf, 1948-1981 (Box 5, Folder 84)
  - Mavromonstakis, G.A., 1939-1945 (Box 5, Folder 85)
  - Maynard, Elliot, 1940-1941 (Box 5, Folder 86)
  - McCabe, Tim L., 1973-2001 (Box 5, Folder 87)
  - McCal-McN, 1941-1989 (Box 5, Folder 88)
  - McDonald, Edward D., 1954 (Box 5, Folder 89)
  - McDonald, Edward D., 1942-1946 (Box 5, Folder 90)
  - McDonald, Mary, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 91)
  - McDunnough, Jim, 1935-1953 (Box 5, Folder 92)
  - McElvare-Rowland, 1942-1961 (Box 5, Folder 93)
  - McFarland, Noel, 1961-1985 (Box 5, Folder 94)
  - McGuffin, W.C., 1957-1977 (Box 5, Folder 95)
  - Me-My, 1941-1995 (Box 5, Folder 96)
  - Menadue, Margaret, 1969-1973 (Box 5, Folder 97)
  - Metzler, Eric H., 1976-1999 (Box 5, Folder 98)
  - Michener, Charles D., 1946-1960 (Box 5, Folder 99)
  - Middlekauff, 1943-1949 (Box 5, Folder 100)
  - Miller, William E., 1955-1964 (Box 5, Folder 101)
  - Monumental Printing Co., 1949-1951 (Box 5, Folder 102)
  - Moore, Harold E., 1969 (Box 5, Folder 103)
  - Moratorio, Mario S., 1970 (Box 5, Folder 104)
  - Moravec, J.A. (Jim), 1976-1994 (Box 5, Folder 105)
  - Morse, Roger A., 1956-1968 (Box 5, Folder 106)
  - Moser, John C., 1954-1998 (Box 5, Folder 107)
  - Mountain Lake Biological Station, 1934-1956 (Box 5, Folder 108)
  - Mueseback, C.F.W., 1942-1962 (Box 5, Folder 109)
  - Muller, Joseph, 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 110)
  - Munro, Hastings, 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 111)
  - Munro, Jean R., 1959-1960 (Box 5, Folder 112)
  - Munroe, Doug, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 113)
  - Munroe Microscope Services, 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 114)
  - Murdoch, Rita, 1964-1969 (Box 5, Folder 115)
  - Munroe, Eugene G., 1942-1984 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Murphy, Henry T., Jr., 1972-1981 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Nabokov, V., 1947-1960 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Na-No, 1946-1993 (Box 6, Folder 4)